(Howard:)A few extra bucks
would be nice.
(Howard:)I could finally move out
of my mother's house.
(Raj:)Where would you go?
(Howard:)I always dreamed about building
a little place of my own
(Howard:)over the garage.
(Raj:)You know, if I made more money,
I could take time off from work
(Raj:)and give pretty girls
submarine rides.
(Howard:)What's that?
(Howard:)Some weird sex thing?
(Howard:)No.
(Raj:)You take pretty girls underwater
(Raj:)in your private submarine,
and you show them fish.
(Raj:)Why does everything
have to be dirty with you?
(Leonard:)I was thinking we could work
on this at night,
(Leonard:)and then maybe
in a couple of weeks,
(Leonard:)we'll have ourselves an app
to sell.
(Howard:)Sounds like
we're in business.
(Raj:)I think we should take a picture
to capture this moment.
(Howard:)Yeah.
Oh!
(Raj(pressing button on camera phone. Camera makes a fart noise):)Was that the best 99 cents
I ever spent, or what?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪